<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gibberish</title>
    <link>https://karthikraobr.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gibberish</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>karthik.0703@gmail.com (Kaarthik)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>karthik.0703@gmail.com (Kaarthik)</webMaster>
    <copyright>© Copyright 2017</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://karthikraobr.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I hate Go</title>
      <link>https://karthikraobr.github.io/post/whyihatego/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>karthik.0703@gmail.com (Kaarthik)</author>
      <guid>https://karthikraobr.github.io/post/whyihatego/</guid>
      <description>Here are a few reasons why I hate Go:
Syntax In my previous post I raved about how Go has a clean syntax, but here are a few reaons why I hate it :
 Anything that starts with a uppercase is exported i.e. it is accessible from outside a package. Names starting with a lowercase are not exported.
 No built-in enum support. As a developer with some background in C# I miss enums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I love Go</title>
      <link>https://karthikraobr.github.io/post/whyilovego/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>karthik.0703@gmail.com (Kaarthik)</author>
      <guid>https://karthikraobr.github.io/post/whyilovego/</guid>
      <description>I was introduced to Go by Bjoern as a part of my student job and I have been smitten by it ever since. Here are a few reason&amp;rsquo;s why I love go, in no particular order :
Fast Compilation Most popular languages are atleast a decade old and do not take advantage of the newer hardware. But, Go on the other hand is designed to run on modern computers and takes advantages of the faster hardware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The art of procrastination</title>
      <link>https://karthikraobr.github.io/post/procrastination/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>karthik.0703@gmail.com (Kaarthik)</author>
      <guid>https://karthikraobr.github.io/post/procrastination/</guid>
      <description>I have been thinking of updating my blog for more than a month now and you all guessed it right, I procrastinated. What better way to update it, than write a post about procrastination. When someone asks me &amp;ldquo;What am I good at&amp;rdquo;? my immediate answer would be procrastination. I am full-time procrastinator! I don&amp;rsquo;t understand why I do it and how I do it, but at the end of the day I realize that I wasted it procrastinating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://karthikraobr.github.io/post/helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>karthik.0703@gmail.com (Kaarthik)</author>
      <guid>https://karthikraobr.github.io/post/helloworld/</guid>
      <description>So! los gehts (german for here we go). Hello World! This is usually the first program developers&amp;rsquo; write to get the taste of a new programming language. I am new to blogging and hence this post! Considering how long I have been working with computers, I am pretty late to the blogging scene, but hey better late than never. I still haven&amp;rsquo;t decided what I will be posting here. Stay Tuned, Stay Hungry, Stay Foolish!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://karthikraobr.github.io/pages/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>karthik.0703@gmail.com (Kaarthik)</author>
      <guid>https://karthikraobr.github.io/pages/resume/</guid>
      <description>It appears that you don&#39;t have a PDF plugin. click here to download the PDF file.
   .pdf-container { height: 0; width: 100%; padding-bottom: 129.41%; /* 11/8.5 = 1.2941 */ overflow: hidden; position: relative; } .pdf-container object { width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; } </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://karthikraobr.github.io/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>karthik.0703@gmail.com (Kaarthik)</author>
      <guid>https://karthikraobr.github.io/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey there! I am Kaarthik. I was born in the garden city of India - Bangalore and have lived a major part of my life there. Currently I live in Paderborn, a small city in Germany where I am pursuing my masters in computer science. I also work part-time for Diebold Nixdorf in their Research &amp;amp; Innovation department.
I got my first computer when I was in my seventh grade and ever since I have been hooked to them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>