<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Gibberish</title>
    <link>https://kaarthik.dev/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Gibberish</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kaarthik.dev/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Running</title>
      <link>https://kaarthik.dev/post/running/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaarthik.dev/post/running/</guid>
      <description>I didn&amp;rsquo;t enjoy running until recently. I would occasionally run a 10k and train for a week or two prior to that and that would be it. Once I moved to Berlin, one of the first things I did apart from hunting for houses was to sign up for the Berlin Half-marathon with a friend of mine. That was a life changing experience. Allow me to explain.
Stress buster When I started, I always thought that running was just about having a strong pair of legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 - In the rearview mirror</title>
      <link>https://kaarthik.dev/post/2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 12:22:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaarthik.dev/post/2018/</guid>
      <description>2018 was quite an eventful year in my life. This year went by even before I could realize it. Here are a few highlights of my life during 2018
Masters Finally, I graduated from the University of Paderborn with a Masters degree in Computer Science 😌. Usually, it takes a normal human being ~2.5 years to complete it, but being the lazy sloth that I am, it took me 3. According to the German law, I can now prefix my name with an M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My relationship with Go</title>
      <link>https://kaarthik.dev/post/whyilovego/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaarthik.dev/post/whyilovego/</guid>
      <description>I have a love-hate relationship (more love and less hate :P) with any new programming language I pick up. This post describes my relationship with Go.
Why I love it  I was introduced to Go by Bjoern as a part of my student job and I have been smitten by it ever since. Here are a few reason&amp;rsquo;s why I love go, in no particular order :
Fast Compilation Most popular languages are atleast a decade old and do not take advantage of the newer hardware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The art of procrastination</title>
      <link>https://kaarthik.dev/post/procrastination/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaarthik.dev/post/procrastination/</guid>
      <description>I have been thinking of updating my blog for more than a month now and you all guessed it right, I procrastinated. What better way to update it, than write a post about procrastination. When someone asks me &amp;ldquo;What am I good at&amp;rdquo;? my immediate answer would be procrastination. I am a full-time procrastinator! I don&amp;rsquo;t understand why I do it and how I do it, but at the end of the day I realize that I wasted it procrastinating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://kaarthik.dev/post/helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaarthik.dev/post/helloworld/</guid>
      <description>So! los gehts (german for here we go). Hello World! This is usually the first program developers&#39; write to get the taste of a new programming language. I am new to blogging and hence this post! Considering how long I have been working with computers, I am pretty late to the blogging scene, but hey better late than never. I still haven&amp;rsquo;t decided what I will be posting here. Stay Tuned, Stay Hungry, Stay Foolish!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
